# PERSONAL INFORMATION Tuan-Anh Bui

- 💎 Temasek Lab, SUTD, Room 3.719, 8 Somapah Road, Singapore
- +65 87415814 🛛 🔀 <u>bta1489@gmail.com</u>
- 🖰 tuananhbui89.github.io
- Skype tuananhbui89

Linkedin tuananhbui89

## **MOTIVATION**

With strong experience on the industrial environment, I pursue the aims that bring a knowledge from academic research to the real life by a technological product, especially using AI, Computer Vision to improve daily, common activities, to make the world to be a better place. I realize that pursuing Ph.D. is the must-do path to deepen my knowledge and improve the research methodology for this goal.

## RESEARCH **BACKGROUND**

Generative Adversarial Network, Deep model Compression, Image Retrieval.

Digital Signal Processing, Audio Processing (Viettel).

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# 2017 - Present Reseacher Assistant on Computer Vision

Temasek Lab, Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD)

- (Present) Deep model compression, esp. in Recurrent Neural Network (RNN) and Long-Short Term Memory (LSTM), to reducing memory and computational cost, to apply on mobile hardware such as FPGA.
- (Present) Improving Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs), esp. in mode collapse problem.
- Implemented module to detect and track Undefined Flying Objects, esp. Drone in Sky Surveillance - Flying Object Detection (SSFOD) project.
- Improved image retrieval module to handle big dataset (appr. 200k images) in Urban-area Scene Based Localization (USBL) project.

# 2012 - 2017 Digital Signal Processing Engineer

Viettel R&D Institute, Viettel Groups

 Developed baseband processing algorithms: Channel equalization using adaptive filter, Adaptive Noise Cancellation, Digital Pre-Distortion to improve the linearity of radio amplifiers.

# 2010 - 2012 Research Assistant on Networking

Undergraduate Research, Green Networking Lab, HUST

 Researched on methods for reducing energy consumption in data centre network using Software Defined Network (SDN).

November 8, 2018 Page 1 / 3

### **EDUCATION**

# 2007 - 2012 B.Sc. in Electronics and Telecommunications (Honour)

Hanoi University of Science and Technology (HUST)

- Thesis title: "Research on optimal trade-off between power saving and QoS".
- Thesis grade: 4/4 (10/10) (Best Thesis Award).
- GPA: 8.44/10 (top 5%, Merit for Excellent Graduate Student)

# 2004 - 2007 High school Diploma, Physics Talented Class

Le Hong Phong Gifted High School

Got a Second prize in National Physics Olympiad for High School Students.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming - Tensorflow, Keras.

Matlab, Python, C.

# Algorithms and Math

- Machine learning algorithms, Deep learning models.
- Probability, Statistic, Algebra.

Others - Logical thinking, problem solving mindset.

### **PAPERS**

2018 Ngoc-Trung Tran\*, **Tuan-Anh Bui\***, Ngai-Man Cheung.

Improving GAN with Neighbors Embedding and Gradient Matching.

Accepted to The Thirty-Third AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI-19), acceptance rate 16.2%.

2018 Ngoc-Trung Tran, Tuan-Anh Bui, Ngai-Man Cheung.

Dist-GAN: Improving GAN using distance constraints.

Accepted to European Conference on Computer Vision 2018 (ECCV).

2018 Ngoc-Trung Tran, Dang-Khoa Le Tan, Anh-Dzung Doan, Thanh-Toan Do, **Tuan-Anh Bui**, Mengxuan Tan, Ngai-Man Cheung.

On-device Scalable Image-based Localization via Prioritized Cascade Search and Fast One-Many RANSAC.

Accepted to Transaction on Image Processing 2018 (TIP).

## Proposal Tuan-Anh Bui.

Improving GAN by Discrimination Inspector.

Improving WGAN using Discriminator Continuty.

Disentangled Image Compression by the (Similarity) Force.

Nonlinear Adaptive DNN model compression.

SceneNet: A generative model for generating scene from 6-DOF camera pose.

Auto-generate Football Minimap from live match using Domain Transfer.

November 8, 2018 Page 2 / 3

#### HONOURS & AWARDS

2012-2015 Creative Idea Award for Research and Management at Viettel R&D Institute.

2012 Merit for excellent graduate student, HUST.

2012 Best Thesis Award in Thesis Defence, SET, HUST.

2012 Third prize in Student Conference on Scientific Research.

2007 Second prize in National Physics Olympiad for High School Students.

## **REFERENCES**

# Associate Professor Ngai-Man Cheung, Ph.D. (Supervisor)

Department of Information Systems Technology and Design

Singapore University of Technology and Design

Email: ngaiman\_cheung@sutd.edu.sg

# Associate Professor Thu-Huong Truong, Ph.D. (Ex-Supervisor)

School of Electronics and Telecommunications

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Email: huong.truong@hust.edu.vn

# Dr. Ngoc-Trung Tran (Colleague)

Temasek Lab

Singapore University of Technology and Design

Email: tntrung@gmail.com

November 8, 2018 Page 3 / 3